# ケンリイ KEN KEONG LEE

#### Personal Statement

After 3 years in DRAM design, I am looking for new opportunity within the realm of semiconductor circuit design. I am intrigued with the advance design tools beyond DRAM design such as Systhesis, APR, Pulsic, Analog floor planing, etc. The past 3 years in DRAM design, I was trained in various design task from design row circuitry, spice verification, layout. Through various projects, I was trained in different part of the DRAM design flow. During downtime between projects, I explored various open source circuit design projects such as Skywater, Efabless, Opensource EDA tools.

# WORK EXPERIENCE

Period	$ m Aug~2020\sim$	
Employer	Zentel Japan ゼンテルジャパン 大阪	
Job Title	Senior Engineer 主任技師	
	JEDEC compliant DRAM circuit design, mainly Spice verification. Involved in ~4 projects, including one custom DRAM project. Job scope involves from standard cells, circuit block design, verification. Job task involved layout, digital&Analog circuits. DRAM testing theory, 1C1T row/column redundancy	
Period	Oct 2019 — March 2020	
Employer	Osaka University 大阪大学	
Job Title	Research Assistant	
Neutrinoless double beta decay, cryogenic scintillating sensor, data		
Period	July 2014 — Aug 2014 (Summer placement)	
Employer	Oxford Instrument Tubney Woods, Oxfordshire	
Job Title	SEPnet Student summer placement	
Mentor	Daniel Strange, daniel.strange@oxinst.com	
	2 months internships, cryogenic superconducting magnet, problem solving	

#### Personal Skills

LanguageEnglish(native), Chinese(native), Malay(Fluent),<br/>Japanese(Business, JLPT N2), Cantonese(Conversational),EDA DRAMschematics-Virtuoso, layout-Jedat's ISMO, Calibre, spice-Finesim,<br/>pre/post RC spice, verilog pattern generation,Semiconductor basictransistors-Undergrad, Logics gates-Undergrad, circuit design-current jobSelf Learn EDAOpenROAD - synthesis, floorplan, APR (CTS, routing)<br/>Memory hierarchy, basic instruction set architectureProgramingPython, C/C++, CAD, Labview, LaTeX, Git, Markdown<br/>Pytorch, FEA-ANSYS, KiCAD, ROOT, Geant4

Dilution refrigerator, high pressure vacuum system wire bonder, cumulative 3 months underground laboratory shift

#### EDUCATION

Experiences

	Period	September 2012 — July 2016	
	Degree	MPhys	
	University	University of Southampton	UK
Second Class Honour(Upper Division), £12 000 scholarship tui			ee
		Graduation thesis: Flavour Composition and Energy Spectrum of A	stro-
		physical Neutrino at IceCube	

_		
Period	October 2016 — March 2020	
Course	Experimental Physics*	
University	Osaka University	Japan
	*completion of studies with credits, 3 years 文部科学省 ship, 6 months research assistant Bolometer development for scintillating crystal at cryog	
	Unsupervised learning for data analysis, dilution refrige	
Period	January 2011 — June 2012	
Level	Advance Level	
Institution	Tunku Abdul Rahman College(TARUC)	KL, Malaysia
	3A*1A, full tuition scholarship, pre-university/high scho	ool equivalent
Period	January 2006 — December 2010	
Level	SPM	
Institution	SMK Raja Abdullah	KL, Malaysia
	9A1B, O level equivalent	

## PERSONAL INFORMATION

DOB 13/07/1993 Nationality Malaysian

Visa status 技術·人文知識·国際業務, PR pending

Linkedin.com/pub/ken-keong-lee/9b/18b/885/

Personal Homepage hareyakana.github.io/cv/

## PAST ACHIEVEMENT

High Achiever Award 2012 by TARC Full merit scholarship for A level studies at TARC

National Physics Quiz 2010 Bronze
National Chemistry Quiz 2010 merit
Level 2 Certificate in Book-keeping and Accounts 2010

## Conferences/Articles/etc.

- $\bullet$  Phys. Rev. D 103, 092008 CANDLES Collaboration "Low background measurement in CANDLES-III for studying the neutrino-less double beta decay of  $^{48}\mathrm{Ca}$  "co-authored"
- International workshop on Revealing the history of the universe with underground particle and nuclear research 2019 Tohoku 2019 "Development of Scintillating Bolometer for CANDLES" (Poster) co-authored
- JPS Autumn 2019 meeting "Bolometer Development using Neutron Transmutation Doped Ge in CANDLES for the study of Neutrinoless Double Beta decay" main presenter
- • TAUP 2019 - "Status of  $^{48}\mathrm{Ca}$  double beta decay search and its future prospect in CANDLES" co-presenter

#### Past research projects

Anomaly search through Unsupervised Machine Learning
Neutrinoless Double Beta Decay
Low temperature Bolometer Development
Dark Matter and IceCube experiment
Phd Project
Phd Project
MPhys Project

Neutrino Oscillations Individual Dissertation

Plasmonics Individual Essay

## VOLUNTARY EXPERIENCES

Period March 2010, April 2011

PLACE Ko Bulon and Satun in Thailand

English Camp for under privileged/abused children

# PAST EXCHANGE INVOLVEMENT

Period 2009

PROGRAM Culture Exchange Program with Kumamoto Gakuen University Fuzoku

High School, Japan

Period 2010

PROGRAM Culture Exchange Program with Osaka Furitsu Minoh High School,

Japan